{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Television%20Shows",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20TV%20show%20follows%20the%20story%20of%20Walter%20White%2C%20a%20chemistry%20teacher%20turned%20meth%20manufacturer%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Breaking%20Bad",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Stranger%20Things",
        "The%20Walking%20Dead",
        "Game%20of%20Thrones"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Television%20Shows",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In%20which%20TV%20show%20would%20you%20find%20the%20character%20named%20Dexter%2C%20a%20forensic%20blood%20spatter%20analyst%20and%20vigilante%20serial%20killer%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Dexter",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Breaking%20Bad",
        "Sherlock",
        "Hannibal"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Television%20Shows",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20TV%20show%20is%20set%20in%20the%20fictional%20Seven%20Kingdoms%20of%20Westeros%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Game%20of%20Thrones",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The%20Crown",
        "Stranger%20Things",
        "The%20Mandalorian"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Television%20Shows",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20TV%20show%20set%20in%20the%201980s%20where%20a%20group%20of%20kids%20encounter%20strange%20supernatural%20events%20in%20a%20small%20town%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Stranger%20Things",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The%20X-Files",
        "Dark",
        "Twin%20Peaks"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Television%20Shows",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20TV%20show%20features%20characters%20such%20as%20Phoebe%2C%20Joey%2C%20and%20Ross%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Friends",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The%20Office%20(US)",
        "How%20I%20Met%20Your%20Mother",
        "Parks%20and%20Recreation"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Television%20Shows",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20TV%20show%20centered%20around%20the%20lives%20of%20doctors%20and%20nurses%20at%20the%20Grey%20Sloan%20Memorial%20Hospital%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Grey's%20Anatomy",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "ER",
        "House",
        "Chicago%20Med"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Television%20Shows",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20TV%20show%20is%20about%20a%20high%20school%20chemistry%20teacher%20who%20starts%20cooking%20meth%20to%20provide%20for%20his%20family%20after%20being%20diagnosed%20with%20cancer%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Breaking%20Bad",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The%20Sopranos",
        "Mad%20Men",
        "Better%20Call%20Saul"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Television%20Shows",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20TV%20show%20is%20known%20for%20the%20line%3A%20\"You%20know%20nothing%2C%20Jon%20Snow\"%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Game%20of%20Thrones",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Vikings",
        "The%20100",
        "Outlander"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Television%20Shows",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20TV%20show%20set%20in%20a%20fictional%20paper%20company%20in%20Scranton%2C%20Pennsylvania%3F",
      "correct_answer": "The%20Office%20(US)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Brooklyn%20Nine-Nine",
        "Parks%20and%20Recreation",
        "Arrested%20Development"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Television%20Shows",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20TV%20show%20features%20a%20genius%20consulting%20detective%20named%20Sherlock%20Holmes%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Sherlock",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Elementary",
        "Dexter",
        "Luther"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
